businesstrack.com 2016-04-22

# 

                     Business Track Online Privacy & Cookies Statement
                                          Last Updated: August 18, 2015
First Data Merchant Services Corporation is a subsidiary of First Data Corporation
Protecting the privacy of users of Business Track (including Client Line) is important to us. Our Online
Privacy & Cookies Statement is designed to inform you about our collection and use of personal
information on this website and the associated mobile app. From time to time, First Data Merchant
Services Corporation (referred to in this policy as FDMS) may make changes to this Online Privacy &
Cookies Statement so we encourage you to check back and review it regularly to ensure you are aware
of current practices.
The Online Privacy & Cookies Statement is available on the home page of this website and throughout
the website where you provide us with personal information.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or our use of your personal information, please
contact the First Data Privacy Office at dataprivacyoffice@firstdata.com or (888) 337-0434.
The Personal Information We Collect Through This Site is the Personal Information You Provide to
Us.
The personal information we collect about you on this website is the information that you provide to us.
This information may include, for example, name, mailing address, email address, phone number and
similar information. In some cases you may provide it directly, such as by entering information into an
application or online form, and in some cases you may provide it indirectly, such as the IP address of the
computer or device you use to connect with us online. We may use the personal information you provide
us to:
                                 ation you have requested,
                                       -initiated or authorized transactions,
                                        -added services,
                                                                                                         s,
interesting.
When You Browse the First Data Website, We Do Not Seek to Determine Your Identity.
Personal information, such as your email address, is not included in cookies and is not collected unless
you provide it to us. FDMS does not disclose domain name or aggregate information to third parties other
than vendors who assist us with our website and who are under contractual confidentiality requirements.
From time to time, however, we may disclose this information to fulfill legal or regulatory obligations or if
we determine such disclosure is legally advisable or necessary to protect our rights, the rights of others,
or to prevent harm (for example, for fraud prevention purposes we may confirm that your IP address
matches the location you enter into an online form). In addition, we may aggregate data about users of
our site and use it for statistical or analytic purposes. This information helps us to better understand our
site’s users and how to improve our site and our offerings.
                                                                                                              1

Information about Online Tracking
Some browsers incorporate a Do Not Track feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want
to have your online activity tracked. Tracking is not the same as using or collecting information in
connection with a single website. For these purposes tracking refers to collecting personally identifiable
information from consumers who use or visit a website or online service as they move across different
websites over time.
How browsers communicate the Do Not Track signal is not yet uniform. As a result this site is not yet set
up to interpret or respond to Do Not Track signals communicated by your browser. Even so, as described
more fully throughout this Online Privacy Statement, we limit our use and collection of your personal
information.
For a description of Do Not Track protocols for browsers and mobile devices, or simply to learn more
about the choices available to you, you can visit the All About Do Not Track website:
http://allaboutdnt.com.
Use of Cookies on this Website
This web site may use cookies solely to aggregate information about the pages that users visit so that we
can update and redesign, as necessary, our web site in order to provide you with the most useful
information.
A cookie is a small file, typically of letters and numbers, downloaded on to a device such as a computer
when a user accesses certain websites. Cookies allow a website to recognize a user’s device.
Cookies can expire at the end of a browser session (from when a user opens the browser window to
when they exit the browser) or they can be stored for longer.
Session cookies – allow websites to link the actions of a user during a browser session. They may be
used for a variety of purposes such as remembering what a user has put in their shopping basket as they
browse around a site. They could also be used for security or to facilitate use of webmail. These session
cookies expire after a browser session so would not be stored longer term.
Persistent cookies – are stored on a users’ device in between browser sessions which allows the
preferences or actions of the user over time and across a site (or in some cases across different
websites) to be remembered. Persistent cookies may be used for a variety of purposes including
remembering users’ preferences and choices when using a site or to target advertising.
First and third party cookies – Whether a cookie is ‘first’ or ‘third’ party refers to the website or domain
placing the cookie. First party cookies in basic terms are cookies set by a website visited by the user - the
website displayed in the URL window. Third party cookies are cookies that are set by a domain other than
the one being visited by the user. If a user visits a website and a separate company sets a cookie through
that website this would be a third party cookie.
For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to
manage, block and delete them, see: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.
This website uses the following cookies. You can delete, remove your consent and/or block cookies sent
to you from this website but parts of the website may not then work.
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit
http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
                                                                                                             2

Cookie Name                     Cookie Purpose              More Information
IV_JCT=%2FportalL               Without this cookie, there  None applicable
                                are some areas within the
                                website that will not
                                function properly. There
                                is no personal information
                                stored in this cookie.
Username=value                  Without this cookie, there  None applicable
                                are some areas within the
                                website that will not
                                function properly. There
                                is no personal information
                                stored in this cookie.
We Are Committed to Protecting the Confidentiality of User Information
Our policies limit access to personal user information that is collected from this website to our employees
and agents and the employees and/or agents of our affiliates and business partners who need the
information to fulfill their business responsibilities. FDMS may disclose personal information collected
online to our affiliates and to vendors who assist us with the website. In some cases, this may require
your information to be sent to other countries. By supplying your information on this website, you consent
to your information being transferred across national borders to FDMS and its affiliates, vendors or
agents. Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our contractual requirements for
safeguarding personal information.
Employees and others with duties related to this website must adhere to this Online Privacy & Cookies
Statement. Our employees receive annual training about the privacy policies and procedures of First Data
Corporation and its affiliates and subsidiaries. We appreciate that protecting consumer privacy is a key
part of our trusted relationship with our clients.
Any employee violating this Online Privacy & Cookies Statement may be subject to disciplinary action, up
to and including dismissal.
By using this website, you agree that your use of Business Track is limited to the terms stated in any
applicable agreement you have with your Processor.
We Use Appropriate Security Safeguards.
At FDMS, security is a priority. FDMS employs appropriate measures, including advanced technology, to
protect personal information collected online against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or
destruction. These measures may include, among others, encryption, physical access security, and other
appropriate technologies. FDMS reviews and enhances its security systems as necessary.
This Website is Not Directed at Persons Under the Age of 18.
Our website is not directed at or intended for persons under the age of 18 and FDMS does not knowingly
collect or maintain information at our web site from persons under the age of 18.
This Website May Be Linked to Other Websites.
As you navigate our site, you may click to websites of our affiliated companies or business partners.
Those web sites may have their own online privacy statements or policies. This Online Privacy & Cookies
Statement will not apply when you move to one of these other sites because affiliate privacy practices
and policies are tailored to the products and services offered by the individual affiliate. If you visit the
pages and sites of our affiliated business units please be sure to review the privacy policies applicable to
those sites.
                                                                                                             3

We may create links to third-party websites. Neither First Data nor FDMS is responsible for the privacy
practices employed by any third-party websites. First Data and FDMS’s privacy policies and practices do
not apply to these sites. First Data and FDMS do not guarantee, approve, or endorse any information,
material, services, or products contained on or available through any linked websites. First Data and
FDMS are not responsible for any content on sites linked from or to Business Track. First Data and FDMS
are providing links to those sites as a convenience and your connection to and use of any linked site are
at your own risk.
This Online Privacy & Cookies Statement applies only to the information we collect on Business Track.
This Online Privacy & Cookies Statement does not apply to information we collect through other methods
or sources, including sites owned or operated by our affiliates, vendors or partners.
                                                                                                          4

                                AVISO DE PRIVACIDAD INTEGRAL
FIRST DATA MERCHANT SERVICES MÉXICO, S. DE R.L. DE C.V. (en adelante (“First
Data”), con domicilio ubicado en Jaime Balmes número 11, Torre “D”, Piso 4, Colonia Los
Morales, Delegación Miguel Hidalgo, C.P. 11510, es la Sociedad Responsable (el
“Responsable”), del tratamiento legítimo, uso, almacenamiento y divulgación controlado e
informado de los datos personales, que recabamos para alcanzar los objetivos corporativos a
través de todas las áreas del negocio y reiterar el compromiso con la privacidad y el derecho a
la autodeterminación informativa.
El presente Aviso de Privacidad tiene como objeto informarle sobre el tratamiento que se le
dará a sus datos personales cuando los mismos son recabados, utilizados, almacenados y/o
transferidos por “First Data”, lo cual se lleva a cabo de conformidad con las disposiciones de la
Ley Federal de Protección de Datos Personales en Posesión de los Particulares (en adelante la
“Ley”) y su Reglamento.
       Datos Personales que se recaban
Usted puede navegar por nuestro sitio web sin proporcionarnos los datos, sin embargo, existen
determinadas secciones dentro del mismo en donde puede proporcionar voluntariamente sus
datos. Sus datos pueden ser recabados en diferentes situaciones, ya sea contenidos en un
correo electrónico, en una solicitud de alguno de nuestros productos o servicios obtenidos de
forma personal, telefónica, o por medio de nuestra página web, o los que proporcione, con
miras al establecimiento de una relación jurídica; todos los datos serán tratados tanto dentro
como fuera de México, por “First Data” y/o por sus sociedades controladoras controladas,
filiales, subsidiarias, matrices, o agencias; los cuales pueden ser, cualquiera de los siguientes:
(i) Información de contacto, como: Nombre, Dirección, Fecha de Nacimiento, RFC, CURP,
Número de Teléfono Fijo, Celular y Fax, Correo Electrónico; (ii) Documentación de Identidad,
tales como: Credencial de Elector, Pasaporte, Licencia de Manejo, Cartilla o Cedula
Profesional; (iii) Datos académicos, tales como: Historia académica, título profesional, numero
de cedula profesional, especialidad, certificados académicos; (iv) Datos laborales, tales como:
cargo dentro de la corporación, domicilio, número de teléfono fijo, celular y fax, correo
electrónico, número de seguro social, cv; (v) Información familiar, tales como nombre de
cónyuge, hijos; (vi) Referencias Personales, tales como información de personas no familiares;
(vii) Datos de facturación, tales como: denominación o razón social de la Sociedad a la que se
hará el cargo, domicilio fiscal, RFC, nombre del Representante Legal; (viii) Datos financieros,
tales como: número de identificación de cuentas bancarias, forma de pago, institución
financiera y clabe interbancaria.
       Datos Personales Sensibles
Le informamos que a fin de cumplimiento a las finalidades previstas en el presente Aviso de
Privacidad, ya sea en su calidad de candidato, empleado, cliente o proveedor, First Data no
recaba Datos Personales Sensibles, considerando todos aquellos que puedan afectar la esfera
más íntima del ser humano.
                                                                                                 5

     Finalidades y/o usos de los Datos Personales
Podemos utilizar sus datos personales para diversas finalidades, dependiendo de las
circunstancias particulares en las que se recaban, así como a responder de información y
atención y su servicio. Archivo de registros y expediente de la relación contractual para
seguimiento de servicios futuros, gestión financiera, elaboración y envío de cotizaciones,
formalización de contratos, envío de publicaciones, facturación y cobro, siempre obedeciendo a
la relación que tengamos con Usted y el Aviso de Privacidad especifico que, en su caso, se
haya puesto a su disposición.
     Menores e incapaces
First Data y sus filiales, son una Empresa comprometida con la privacidad de los menores
incapaces; por ello, no recabamos intencionalmente ni tratamos datos personales de menores
e incapaces, cuando no se cuenta con el consentimiento expreso de sus padres, tutores o
representantes legales. Si Usted es padre, tutor o representante legal de un menor o incapaz y
sabe que nos ha proporcionado datos personales sin su consentimiento, podrá solicitar que los
mismos sean cancelados a la siguiente dirección de correo electrónico:
privacidaddedatos@firstdata.com
     Uso de tecnologías de seguimiento
Cuando usted navega en nuestro sitio web se recaba cierta información no personal por medio
de “cookies” y de los “registros del servidor” o “web beacons”. La obtención de esta
información se da por el simple uso e interacción con nuestro sitio de Internet y la información
que se recaba puede consistir en direcciones de Protocolo de Internet, su sistema operativo,
tipo de navegador, información sobre su ubicación (proporcionada por dispositivos móviles) y la
ruta que Usted sigue durante el tiempo que pasa en nuestro sitio.
Estos datos se recaban únicamente con los siguientes propósitos: generar estadísticas
relativas a las visitas a nuestro sitio web, al tiempo que pasa en el mismo, y los sitios de
referencia que puedan haberle traído al nuestro. Esta información también se utiliza para
mantener y actualizar los perfiles de los usuarios y para adecuar o personalizar la información
que se proporciona por este medio.
     Transferencias de Datos Personales
First Data podrá transferir sus Datos personales a terceros ya sea personas físicas o morales
distintas a esta Sociedad, con los que mantenga una relación jurídica, únicamente con el fin de
cumplir con las finalidades descritas en el Aviso de Privacidad. First Data también podrá
transferir sus datos personales en los casos específicamente previstos en la Ley, en este
sentido su información puede ser compartida con: (i) Compañias de Seguros; (ii) Sociedades
que operen junto con First Data algún tipo de software y cualquier infraestructura de informática
que sirva de plataforma para mantener actualizadas y protegidas sus bases de datos; (iii)
proveedores de mensajería; (iv) Proveedores de administración de nómina; (v) Proveedores
                                                                                                6

que realizan la destrucción de la documentación física proporcionada para cumplir con los fines
del servicio proporcionado; y (vi) Agencias de Cobranza.
La autorización del Titular conforme a esta sección, faculta al Responsable y/o sus Encargados
a transmitir Datos Personales del Titular a dichos proveedores, en el entendido de que estos
últimos están obligados a través de los contratos correspondientes, a mantener la
confidencialidad de los Datos Personales suministrados por el Responsable y/o sus
Encargados y a observar el presente Aviso de Privacidad.
First Data, se compromete a no transferir su información personal a terceros sin su
consentimiento, salvo las excepciones previstas en Ley Federal de Datos Personales en
Posesión de los Particulares y su Reglamento, así como a realizar esta transferencia en los
términos que fijan dichos ordenamientos.
     Medidas de Seguridad
First Data ha adoptado medidas de seguridad, administrativas, técnicas y físicas, necesarias y
a su alcance para proteger los datos personales contra daño, perdida, alteración, destrucción o
el uso, acceso o tratamiento no autorizado.
     Derechos con respecto a sus Datos Personales
Como titular de datos personales, usted puede ejercitar ante el Responsable de Datos
Personales de First Data, los derechos de acceso, rectificación, cancelación y oposición
(derechos “ARCO”). Asimismo, puede revocar, en todo momento, el consentimiento que haya
otorgado y que fuere necesario para el tratamiento de sus datos, así como limitar el uso o
divulgación de los mismos.
Lo anterior, a través del envío de su solicitud en los términos establecidos por la Ley al correo
electrónico: privacidaddedatos@firstdata.com o al domicilio especificado en el primer párrafo
del presente.
Para su fácil referencia, se describen brevemente los derechos ARCO:
- Acceso.- que se le informe cuáles de sus datos personales están contenidos en las bases de
datos de First Data, para qué se utilizan dichos datos personales, el origen y las
comunicaciones que se hayan realizado con los mismos y, en general, las condiciones y
generalidades del tratamiento.
- Rectificación.- que se corrijan o actualicen sus datos personales en caso de que sean
inexactos o incompletos.
- Cancelación.- que sus datos personales sean dados de baja, total o parcialmente, de las
bases de datos de First Data cuando considere que los mismos no están siendo tratados
conforme a los principios y deberes que establece la Ley.
                                                                                                7

- Oposición.- oponerse por causa legítima al tratamiento de sus datos personales.
Si desea conocer los requisitos y procedimientos para el ejercicio de derechos ARCO, le
pedimos contacte al Responsable de Datos Personales de First Data.
     Cambios al Aviso de Privacidad
Los cambios sustanciales en el presente Aviso de Privacidad, le serán comunicados a través
de nuestro sitio web: www.firstdata.com.mx
     Contacto
En caso de tener dudas o comentarios respecto al Aviso de Privacidad, le pedimos contacte al
Departamento de Protección de Datos Personales (COMPLIANCE), a través de la siguiente
dirección de correo electrónico privacidaddedatos@firstdata.com, o en la dirección antes
especificada.
Fecha de última actualización: Agosto 2015
                                                                                           8
